Imagine having to wear this to the Met.
Imagine going to the Met in 2024.
Imagine seeing the tone of the world shifting the way that it is.
People finally waking up and crying out about pollution, corruption and overproduction,
about genocide and proxy wars, about resource theft and child labor.
Imagine seeing all this happening before your very eyes and thinking,
and you know what the world needs to be paying attention to right now?
Me and my silly hat.
Look at my hat, everybody. Isn't it just something?
Imagine spending $75,000 on a ticket and God knows how much money, time, energy to play dress up as a monument to opulence
and some kind of twisted, fucked up Hunger Games cosplay during a time when even the obedient people,
even the people who did what they were told or looking at a future where they might not be able to do basic things like
own a home, start a family or ever retire.
Imagine seeing the president of a Western-backed, UN-recognized country publicly declare his intentions to commit
yet more war crimes on the very same night and think,
but I've already bought my hat.
I can't cancel. They have to see it.
Tonight is about me and my hat.
Shame.